[
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9901_0023_agreatmovement",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 26,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9901_0023_d_00_container_agreatmovement",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9903_MSQ_Emile",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_23",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_22",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9901_0023_agreatmovement_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Allies for the New Order",
        "Description": "Try to convince the factions to join your cause, starting with the Covenant. Speak to a Covenant leader in Brightwood.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"We need more Soulwardens.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Indeed. I know a place we could set a camp, and I might even have a few candidates already.\\n\\nBut even if they become Wardens, let's be honest  - we won't have the forces to counter the Tempest.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Oh, good luck with those Covenant people. \\n\\nI'd say they're crazy, but I suppose that's exactly the kind of allies we're looking for.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Oh, hello! I am Émile, er, Templar d'Aquitane, or even Lieutenant Templar General, in fact. Fourth Battalion.\\n\\nI am quite occupied at the moment, re-examining the Covenant's priorities.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9903_0024_alostcause",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9903_0024_d_00_container_alostcause",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9903_MSQ_Emile",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_24",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9903_0024_alostcause_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Spark of Hope",
        "Description": "Defeat the creature in Brightrest Cemetery as a favor to the Covenant.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"The factions must unite.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Unite? A beautiful dream, but I have no time to indulge in dreams right now.\\n\\nI must attend to a pressing matter - reports of an especially foul Lost stalking Brightrest Cemetery.",
        "InProgressResponse": "If the creature is too much for you, there is no shame in that. \\n\\nThe Spark will eventually shine its light on a way to defeat it. I hope so… at least.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Magnificent! I should have recognized that you are not someone to make idle promises.\\n\\nI suppose I am inclined to hear you out - you say the factions must unite against Corruption, but under what banner?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9903_0025_chainofcommand",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9903_0025_d_00_container_chainofcommand",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9903_MSQ_Emile",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_25",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_24",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9903_0025_chainofcommand_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Chain of Command",
        "Description": "You've gained Émile's support. Deliver his letter of recommendation to General Carvalho of the Covenant.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Where can I find General Carvalho?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "He would be at Ballard's Manor, the temporary center of operations for the Fourth Battalion.\\n\\nI will even send word ahead to inform him of the assistance you gave us here. You have inspired me, I think.",
        "InProgressResponse": "You will find General Carvalho in Ballard's Manor. He's a good man.\\n\\nI look forward to hearing how the conversation goes.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Oh, thank the Spark you're safe! I heard news just after you departed that the General's camp had fallen.\\n\\nIt is a tremendous blow to our forces here. And even worse, it means… I am in charge.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9903_0026_heartsandsouls",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9903_0026_d_00_container_heartsandsouls",
        "NpcDestinationId": "NPC_9902_MSQ_Yonas",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_26",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_25",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9903_0026_heartsandsouls_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Covenant Commitment",
        "Description": "Return to Yonas with news of your success with the Covenant.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Then join me against Corruption.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Zut! I set myself up for that, didn't I? I will have to consider further and consult with other Covenant officers.\\n\\nBut I promise you this, I will at least attend your parley, if that is what you ask of me.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I look forward to seeing you again at the parley, {playerName}. \\n\\nMay the Spark guide your steps until then.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Well, what do you think of our new camp? Not much to look at yet, but as Plato says, the beginning is the most important part of the work. \\n\\nThough this fort seems familiar, somehow…have I been here before?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9901_0027_thesyndicatesupport",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 30,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9901_0027_d_00_container_thesyndicatesupport",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9904_MSQ_Theophrastus",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_27",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_26",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9901_0027_thesyndicatesupport_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "The Syndicate's Support",
        "Description": "One faction down, two to go. Speak to a Syndicate leader in Weaver's Fen after reaching Level 30.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"They're willing to parley.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Really? That is certainly a surprise - you seem to be quite a recruiter, my protege.\\n\\nIf the Covenant will talk, perhaps these other warmongering, flag-wavers will too. Who's next?",
        "InProgressResponse": "I know I've seen some of those Syndicate types around these parts.\\n\\nMaybe in the swamps to the east?",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Um, you'll have to give me a moment! Now, where's that test flask? \\n\\nAnd then I just need the botanical sheathes to collect the fumes, and then, our troubles will be over!",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9904_0028_thenoseknows_V2",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 32,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9904_0028_d_00_container_thenoseknows_V2",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9914_MSQ_Hunter",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_27b",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_27",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9904_0028_thenoseknows_V2_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "9904_0028_thenoseknowsa_V2",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "The Nose Knows",
        "Description": "Find someone who can make bear repellent, as a favor to Dr. Theophrastus and the Syndicate. Then, distribute the repellent to the researchers in the field.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Nice to meet you. I'm {playerName}.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Hmm, yes, well. This has been a stimulating conversation, but I must get back to work. \\n\\nWith this news of Corruption spreading southward, I may need to relocate soon.",
        "InProgressResponse": "The phosphorus in these urine samples is elevated…it even glows in the dark. Fascinating. \\n\\nBut will it suffice for the repellant? I need an expert.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Heard you tromping through the brush from yards out. Thought you were one of those Syndicate clowns.\\n\\n They scare off the game.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9904_0028_thenoseknowsa_V2",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 32,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9904_0028_d_00_container_thenoseknowsa_V2",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9915_MSQ_Researcher1",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_27c",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_27b",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9904_0028_thenoseknowsa_V2_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "9904_0028_thenoseknowsb",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "A Breakthrough with Bears",
        "Description": "Find someone who can make bear repellent, as a favor to Dr. Theophrastus and the Syndicate. Then, distribute the repellent to the researchers in the field.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Do you happen to know how to make bear repellent?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Bear repellent? Sure, easy enough. There's an old recipe that hunters here have used for ages. Here, take it. \\n\\nThose Syndicate folk…if you ask me, they're so concerned with being logical they forget to be practical.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Now I can avoid accidentally stepping on those field researchers…because they reek of bear urine.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Wow, urine! Just what I needed!",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9904_0028_thenoseknowsb",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 32,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9904_0028_d_00_container_thenoseknowsb",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9916_MSQ_Researcher2",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_27d",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_27c",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9904_0028_thenoseknowsb_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "9904_0028_thenoseknowsc",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Skulking in the Fen",
        "Description": "Find someone who can make bear repellent, as a favor to Dr. Theophrastus and the Syndicate. Then, distribute the repellent to the researchers in the field.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9904_0028_thenoseknowsb_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9904_0028_thenoseknowsb_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "My friends still need bear repellent, if you don't mind.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Did Theo finally figure out the formula? Thank science for that…",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9904_0028_thenoseknowsc",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 32,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9904_0028_d_00_container_thenoseknowsc",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9917_MSQ_Researcher3",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_27e",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_27d",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9904_0028_thenoseknowsc_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "9904_0028_thenoseknowsd",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Brushes with Bears",
        "Description": "Find someone who can make bear repellent, as a favor to Dr. Theophrastus and the Syndicate. Then, distribute the repellent to the researchers in the field.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9904_0028_thenoseknowsc_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9904_0028_thenoseknowsc_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9904_0028_thenoseknowsc_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Ugh, this smells terrible. \\n\\nThe things I do for data...",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9904_0028_thenoseknowsd",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 32,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9904_0028_d_00_container_thenoseknowsd",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9918_MSQ_Researcher4",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_27f",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_27e",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9904_0028_thenoseknowsd_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "9904_0028_thenoseknowse",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Beating about the Bushes",
        "Description": "Find someone who can make bear repellent, as a favor to Dr. Theophrastus and the Syndicate. Then, distribute the repellent to the researchers in the field.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9904_0028_thenoseknowsd_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9904_0028_thenoseknowsd_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "My friends still need bear repellent. It reeks, but it's better than getting mauled by a bear.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Ah, it's almost a shame. I think the bears were about to accept me, maybe.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9904_0028_thenoseknowse",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 32,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9904_0028_d_00_container_thenoseknowse",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9904_MSQ_Theophrastus",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_28",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_27f",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9904_0028_thenoseknowse_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Dr. Theo's Thesis",
        "Description": "Find someone who can make bear repellent, as a favor to Dr. Theophrastus and the Syndicate. Then, distribute the repellent to the researchers in the field.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9904_0028_thenoseknowse_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9904_0028_thenoseknowse_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9904_0028_thenoseknowse_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Oh, you're back? Do you know much about urine? \\n\\nI can't figure out where I've gone wrong! Not enough sulfur? It certainly smells bad enough already…",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9904_0029_thestormwall",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9904_0029_d_00_container_thestormwall",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9904_MSQ_Theophrastus",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_29",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_28",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9904_0029_thestormwall_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "The Storm's Source",
        "Description": "Dr. Theophrastus has asked you to continue his research at the Lepus ruins. Investigate the phenomenon and report back to him.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What's your theory?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Well, it began when I was studying the Stormwall that surrounds the island.\\n\\nWe've always taken it for granted that the Stormwall is caused by Corruption, but what if it's more… environmental?",
        "InProgressResponse": "Did you find the source of the mini-storm? \\n\\nWell then, you have to keep looking!",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You found it? Incredible! A storm, however small, projected by the collective consciousness of the earth itself! Terra cogitatum! \\n\\nAnd you realize what this means about the Stormwall encircling the island, yeah?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9904_0030_twodown",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9904_0030_d_00_container_twodown",
        "NpcDestinationId": "NPC_9902_MSQ_Yonas",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_30",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_29",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9904_0030_twodown_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Two Down",
        "Description": "You've convinced the Syndicate to come to the negotiating table. Return to Yonas with the good news.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"This is why the factions must unite.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Oh... that again? Just when we've made this discovery? This might even explain the Blight!\\n\\nI suppose you did make this possible, however… Fine. How do you propose we unite the factions?",
        "InProgressResponse": "Oh, you again? I promise I will speak with other Alchemists.\\n\\nI just need to finish my work here first.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Welcome home, {playerName}! I've been busy recruiting new Wardens.\\n\\nOur little family is growing by the day. I don't suppose you had any luck with the plague-people, did you?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9901_0031_themaraudersupport",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 35,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9901_0031_d_00_container_themaraudersupport",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9905_MSQ_Rima",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_31",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_30",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9901_0031_themaraudersupport_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "The Marauders' Support",
        "Description": "Only one faction left to convince. Speak to a Marauder leader in Cutlass Keys after reaching Level 35.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"They're the only faction left.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Yes, and the most aggressive, from what I've been told. No hierarchy to organize them. \\n\\nGetting warriors like that to come to the table will be difficult.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Make sure you're in top form before going to Cutlass Keys. \\n\\nOur plan will backfire if you get humiliated.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Hm. A new face, but not a complete mystery -  I've heard of your name and your feats. You are strange.\\n\\nI am Rima Bahar, a committed Marauder, and many people also find me strange. Perhaps we'll get along.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9905_0032_invalhalla",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 36,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9905_0032_d_00_container_invalhalla",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9905_MSQ_Rima",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_32",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_31",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9905_0032_invalhalla_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "The Heart of Conflict",
        "Description": "The Marauders respect individual strength, do they? Enter their Proving Grounds and demonstrate your prowess to Rima.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"You should be fighting Corruption.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Oh, but we ARE fighting Corruption. Here in the fighting pit, we test ourselves against those twisted creatures. \\n\\nOf course, there is one among the Corrupted whom we all fear to fight. \\n\\nThat monster, Thorpe.",
        "InProgressResponse": "We prove ourselves with weapons, not words.\\n\\nCome now, I will enjoy seeing you in action.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Well, someone has proven themselves! I saw you fight - your moves are like the notes of a beautiful song.\\n\\nI am composing the melody in my head, already. Others are talking about you as well, {playerName}.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9905_0033_stillwerise",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9905_0033_d_00_container_stillwerise",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9905_MSQ_Rima",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_33",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_32",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9905_0033_stillwerise_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Still, We Rise",
        "Description": "Yrsa, the current champion of the Proving Grounds, is missing. Find out what happened to her.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Where is she?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "She's... hmm, that's strange, she should have arrived by now. \\n\\nShe is the type who likes to make an entrance, but…",
        "InProgressResponse": "Did you find Yrsa? Six feet tall, white-blonde hair, moves like a tiger in the dusk…mmm. \\n\\nI feel a song growing. Yrsa deserves an epic.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "There you are, {playerName}. But where is Yrsa? The champion of my own heart…",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9905_0034_thealliance",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9905_0034_d_00_container_thealliance",
        "NpcDestinationId": "NPC_9902_MSQ_Yonas",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_34",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_33",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9905_0034_thealliance_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "The Alliance",
        "Description": "All three factions have agreed to talk. Return to Yonas with the news.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Yes. Let's fight the Corrupted together.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Together? Is this the Soulwarden \"alliance\" I have been hearing about?\\n\\nI know some Marauders who have rallied to the cause, and perhaps now, I will do so, as well.",
        "InProgressResponse": "The time for words is over now. \\n\\nFor Yrsa, and for those who can't fight, we will fight, and we will win.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Well now, our peacemaker returns! We already heard that some Marauders have agreed to parley. Well done!\\n\\nWe've received a more troubling dispatch as well, from a warlord among the Corrupted - he mentions you by name.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9901_0035_herewestand",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 40,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9901_0035_d_00_container_herewestand",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9919_MSQ_WardenScout",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_35",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_34",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9901_0035_herewestand_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Answer the Call",
        "Description": "You've decided to answer Commander Thorpe's personal challenge. Travel to Restless Shore. There, you'll meet up with the Soulwarden scouts who are currently surveilling Thorpe in his lair, the Depths.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Do we know where he is?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "In Restless Shore. I've been dispatching most new Wardens to hold the lines in Great Cleave and Shattered Mountain.\\n\\nBut I've sent some of our best scouts to look for weaknesses in Thorpe's base.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Hurry back, will you? Who knows how long I'll be able to keep the factions from each others' throats without you.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Keep your voice down! Thorpe has eyes and ears all over Restless Shore.\\n\\nI'm the last Warden scout left - the others let their guard down. Thorpe found them.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9901_0036_masterofthetempest",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 40,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9901_0036_d_00_container_masterofthetempest",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9919_MSQ_WardenScout",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_36",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_35",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9901_0036_masterofthetempest_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Into the Depths",
        "Description": "Finally, the battle with Commander Thorpe has arrived. Make your way through the Depths and take him down.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"So everyone else is dead?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Dead or worse. Thorpe's Corrupted took them - they were torturing them.\\n\\nThe screaming only stopped this morning. The plan now is to retreat.",
        "InProgressResponse": "If you do find Thorpe… make him suffer.\\n\\nIf I live six more centuries, I'll never forget those cries…",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You… you survived…? And your eyes, you're not even Corrupted.\\n\\nDid you find him? Did you actually defeat Thorpe?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9901_0036_masterofthetempest_v2",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 40,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9901_0036_d_00_container_masterofthetempest_v2",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9919_MSQ_WardenScout",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_36",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_35",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9901_0036_masterofthetempest_v2_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Into the Depths",
        "Description": "Finally, the battle with Commander Thorpe has arrived. Make your way through the Depths and take him down.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"So everyone else is dead?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Dead or worse. Thorpe's Corrupted took them - they were torturing them.\\n\\nThe screaming only stopped this morning. The plan now is to retreat.",
        "InProgressResponse": "If you do find Thorpe… make him suffer.\\n\\nIf I live six more centuries, I'll never forget those cries…",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You… you survived…? And your eyes, you're not even Corrupted.\\n\\nDid you find him? Did you actually defeat Thorpe?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9901_0036_masterofthetempest_solo",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 40,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9901_0036_d_00_container_masterofthetempest_solo",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_36_b",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_36_b_Unlock",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9901_0036_masterofthetempest_solo_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Hounding the Master",
        "Description": "As an alternative to challenging Thorpe in the Depths Expediton, Work with Titus to draw the Tyrant out so that you may fight him on your own terms.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "",
        "InProgressResponse": "",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9919_0037_planb",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9919_0037_d_00_container_planb",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9905c_MSQ_Rima",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_37",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_36",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9919_0037_planb_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Triumphant Return",
        "Description": "Return triumphantly to Fort Alazar with news of your victory over Thorpe.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What's going on there?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "From the sound of things, nothing good. More Corrupted, stronger Corrupted, coming south from the Shattered Mountain. \\n\\nThe Wardens are losing their footing there as well.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Hurry. Don't worry about me. I'll be fine.\\n\\nGood luck with the parley. Hope you're as good at talking as you are at fighting!",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Stay back, Soulwarden! Has that vile woman claimed your soul as well? \\n\\nI warn you, if you're here to finish the job, I will not go down without a fight!",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9905_0038_itstrueface",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 42,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9905_0038_d_00_container_itstrueface",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9903c_MSQ_Emile",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_38",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_37",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9905_0038_itstrueface_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Its True Face",
        "Description": "Fort Alazar lies in ruins, but it might not be too late to save Yonas and Émile. Follow their trail northwest, into the mountains.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"She destroyed the camp?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Not her. Your fellow Soulwardens - she enthralled them, drove them mad. They turned on us - she didn't even lift a finger. \\n\\nTheir rage… her smile… may I never see anything so terrible again.",
        "InProgressResponse": "If there's one thing I hate, it's being made to look like a fool. \\n\\nThat cursed woman has made fools of us all.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Oh, praise the Spark! I don't know who - or what - the hell that was. \\n\\nThat thing… it wore a woman's form, but it wasn't like any woman I've known.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9903_0039_aherosduty",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 43,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9903_0039_d_00_container_aherosduty",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9903c_MSQ_Emile",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_39",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_38",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9903_0039_aherosduty_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "A Hero's Duty",
        "Description": "Maybe it's not too late to save Yonas. Go into the cave after him and the mysterious woman.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Where's Yonas?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "He's inside the cave. I-I went in, but it was too late...\\n\\nI think he was a friend of yours… I'm sorry.",
        "InProgressResponse": "He… spoke very highly of you, before… everything happened.\\n\\nIt's just… I'm so sorry.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "I see your pain. I know it's small consolation, but you're not the first who's had to put down a friend.\\n\\nNot the last either, I suspect. That demon-woman… was that the one they call the Tempest?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9903_0040_emilesrequest",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 44,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9903_0040_d_00_container_emilesrequest",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9903d_MSQ_Emile",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_40",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_39",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9903_0040_emilesrequest_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Émile's Request",
        "Description": "Yonas is gone, but you and Émile are determined to track down his killer. Meet him in the tavern in Restless Shore.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"We still can. We will.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Hah. Good. If you're not giving up, neither am I. \\n\\nEven if the alliance lies in ruins, even if the Covenant withdraws, I will not abandon you.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I will see you in Restless Shore, {playerName}.\\n\\nTake time to grieve if you need it.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Ah, it is good to see you again, Warden. I believe you and Dr. Theo here know each other? \\n\\nBefore we get down to business, we should honor your friend, the old man… Yonas, was it? Yes, a toast to Yonas.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9903_0041_somethinglefttosave",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9903_0041_d_00_container_somethinglefttosave",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9903d_MSQ_Emile",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_41",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_40",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9903_0041_somethinglefttosave_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "The Story Behind the Name",
        "Description": "Investigate the Arclight Cavern for clues about the mysterious Captain Isabella.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Isabella... and a box?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Yes, that coincidence struck me too. To find mention of both, in the same story... \\n\\nBut that was a hundred years ago. After Isabella's lover stole her soul, they both vanished.",
        "InProgressResponse": "If you want to hear a story, buy a drink for a local. \\n\\nThough the stories about this Isabella do get more far-fetched, as the night goes on.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Aha! It is good to see you. I hope I did not send you after a tall tale.\\n\\nDid you find the cave? Any information at all about this box?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9905_0042_shecameback",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 46,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9905_0042_d_00_container_shecameback",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9905d_MSQ_Rima",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_42",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_41",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9905_0042_shecameback_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "She Came Back",
        "Description": "You didn't expect to see Rima again after the fall of Fort Alazar, yet here she is. Talk to her at the bar.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Rima is here?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Yes, she is a very famous singer, you know? Her song about the moon…it can move the heart of any man, or woman. \\n\\nSometimes both at once, I've heard… but yes, you should go speak to her.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I'm glad to know that Rima is, after all, a woman of integrity.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Hello, hero. You come here often? \\n\\nThe seafood is good, but the sea does not draw me. I seek my inspiration in closer things.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9905_0043_foragoodcause",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 47,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9905_0043_d_00_container_foragoodcause",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9909_MSQ_AEVillager3",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_43",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_42",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9905_0043_foragoodcause_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Natural Inspiration",
        "Description": "Rima has asked you to go commune with nature in Restless Shore. She probably has a good reason.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"You need a cause now?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "\"Need\" is a strong word. But the cause is just, and you still intrigue me.\\n\\nIf nothing else, it might make for a great song. We just need some inspiration.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Do you think my suggestion is silly? Humor me, and go there anyway.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Good. The human Rima said you'd come. \\n\\nI am Range, and you are {playerName}.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9909_0044_mothertongue",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 48,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9909_0044_d_00_container_mothertongue",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9905d_MSQ_Rima",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_44",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_43",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9909_0044_mothertongue_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Mother Tongue",
        "Description": "A talking wolf has asked for your help. Return to Rima and share the message.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Is this about the box?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "That’s right. Compared to my brethren, I range far, and see farther. \\n\\nEvery day, Corruption spreads and the Tempest’s reach grows. Soon, she will discover where the Angry Earth has hidden her soul.",
        "InProgressResponse": "We've hidden the box at the Motherwell, one of our sacred sites. \\n\\nIn normal times, humans who go there are killed on sight, but these are not normal times. \\n\\nPlease, go help my brothers and sisters.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You heard the earth whisper, didn't you? I had a feeling you would. \\n\\nIt's a rare skill, to truly listen. Most people go their whole lives without knowing any voice but their own.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9905_0045_thebox",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 50,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9905_0045_d_00_container_thebox",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9902b_MSQ_Adiana",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_45",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_44",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9905_0045_thebox_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Race for the Box",
        "Description": "The box is in Edengrove. Quickly, find it before Isabella does.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Are you coming?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "I don't think the Angry Earth would welcome so many humans into its sacred places at once. \\n\\nMaybe I'll go with Émile, to the front lines. It might be refreshing to fight the Corrupted in a real battle.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I know our paths will cross again, {playerName}. I'm looking forward to it.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You… you again? The one to whom I gave the Living Seed? It seems a lifetime ago.\\n\\nIf I recall, you had committed yourself to battle Corruption. I wish I had done the same.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9902_0046_stemthetide",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9902_0046_d_00_container_stemthetide",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9902b_MSQ_Adiana",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_46",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_45",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9902_0046_stemthetide_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Stem the Tide",
        "Description": "Adiana has asked you to help protect the Angry Earth sanctuary. Go to the Motherwell and hold off the blight invasion.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Where is the box now?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "It is gone. This queen of Corruption, the Tempest as she is called by humans, she has taken it.\\n\\nAnd with it in her possession, we cannot resist her. Even the Motherwell is failing.",
        "InProgressResponse": "The sanctuary seal - we need your help. I will not beg…",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "The Motherwell is safe then? Yes, you have proven again to be above suspicion. \\n\\nYou hear the earth's language now, don't you? That is why you were chosen to save the Motherwell.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9904_0047_greatminds",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 51,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9904_0047_d_00_container_greatminds",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9904d_MSQ_Theophrastus",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_47",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_46",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9904_0047_greatminds_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Great Minds",
        "Description": "Dr. Theophrastus has set up camp in Edengrove, and he has some interesting ideas on how to protect the Motherwell sanctuary. Go speak to him.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"How can we stop it?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "There is another human here who thinks he knows a way - an Alchemist. He arrived a short time ago. \\n\\nHe has many strange ideas. Some of them may even be worth listening to.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Have you spoken to the Alchemist yet? \\n\\nHis camp is just a little ways from here.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "{playerName}! I had a feeling you'd find your way here. Great minds, great minds! \\n\\nThis place is beyond my wildest dreams. The trees, the water… the Dryads. If only I could touch them…",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9904_0048_enemyofmyenemy",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 52,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9904_0048_d_00_container_enemyofmyenemy",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9902b_MSQ_Adiana",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_48",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_47",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9904_0048_enemyofmyenemy_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Enemy of my Enemy",
        "Description": "Deploy Dr. Theophrastus's Blighted spore bombs around the sanctuary perimeter.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I don't know. Do you?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "My hypothesis is that the Blight is somehow caused when the energies of Corruption and Angry Earth are mingled.\\n\\nIt is clearly a threat to the Angry Earth, but what about to Corruption?",
        "InProgressResponse": "Isn't Alchemy fun? \\n\\nBut in this case also very, very serious!",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You surrounded the sanctuary with Blight and think that's a form of protection? \\n\\nBut wait… you may be right. I do feel the Corruption receding ever-so-slightly.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9902_0049_recipeforfailure",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 53,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9902_0049_d_00_container_recipeforfailure",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9906_MSQ_Shamaness",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_49",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_48",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9902_0049_recipeforfailure_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Recipe for Destruction",
        "Description": "Adiana has sent you to speak with Ixia, the caretaker of the Motherwell sanctuary.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Won't the Stormwall fail anyways?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "We must attempt to delay that as long as possible. The Corrupted Empress in Ebonscale has amassed a fleet.\\n\\nIf the Stormwall fails for even a moment, they will set sail.",
        "InProgressResponse": "If you wish to borrow the Angry Earth's power, you must ask permission. \\n\\nYou can find Ixia not far from here.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "as bitter witness to the scars of time\\n\\nwe hide our shrinking gardens from the flames \\n\\nand any blood-ripe creatures stumbling in\\nare seen no more",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9906_0050_thescenicroute",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 54,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9906_0050_d_00_container_thescenicroute",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9906_MSQ_Shamaness",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_50",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_49",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9906_0050_thescenicroute_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Ixia's Orders",
        "Description": "Find four rare fungi across Edengrove, and harvest their unique spores.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Yes, Corruption threatens us all.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "so rarely have the blood-ripe creatures heard \\n\\nand even fewer answered nature's call \\n\\nbut as we have been fed, we too must feed\\n\\nwhat do you need?",
        "InProgressResponse": "we watch the earth be split and split again \\n\\nby drift rebellion conquest cosmos war \\n\\nwe think ourself beyond corruption's reach \\n\\nnot anymore",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "as water quenches magma with its death \\n\\nyou wish to turn our death upon itself \\n\\nand make a weapon neither life nor death \\n\\ncan long resist…",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9906_0051_ararespice",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9906_0051_d_00_container_ararespice",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9906_MSQ_Shamaness",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_50b",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_50",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9906_0051_ararespice_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "9906_0050_thescenicrouteb",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Rare Spice",
        "Description": "For the final bomb ingredient, defeat the Dryads at Rafflesia and take their seeds.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Where can I find those seeds?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "the dryad waits where human hands once built\\n\\nthe patient guard of silent sun-mote caves \\n\\na place now only hinted on the wind",
        "InProgressResponse": "in this eternal land death holds no sway \\n\\nbut in the deepest time the husks of things \\n\\nthat even deathless creatures can't recall \\n\\nlie sunken still",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "the parts are gathered and the moon is right \\n\\nthe simmered spores primordial ferment \\n\\nnow tie it tight with dryad's seeds to make \\n\\nthe blighted bomb",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9906_0050_thescenicrouteb",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 54,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9906_0050_thescenicrouteb",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9902b_MSQ_Adiana",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_51",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_50b",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9906_0050_thescenicrouteb_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Armed and Dangerous",
        "Description": "Return to Adiana in Edengrove.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9906_0050_thescenicrouteb_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9906_0050_thescenicrouteb_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9906_0050_thescenicrouteb_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "She chose to help you after all?\\n\\nI admit I wasn't sure that she would.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9902_0052_saboteur",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 55,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9902_0052_d_00_container_saboteur",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9902b_MSQ_Adiana",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_52",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_51",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9902_0052_saboteur_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Saboteur",
        "Description": "Sabotage the Corrupted Fleet at the Dynasty Shipyard.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I'm off to sabotage the fleet.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Even if this works, your plan for the Motherwell is still insane. \\n\\nBut the Corrupted Ebonscale fleet is a very real threat, and I'll breathe easier knowing it's neutralized. \\n\\nGood luck.",
        "InProgressResponse": "The fleet is moored in Ebonscale, at the Dynasty Shipyards. \\n\\nExpect it to be very well-defended.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "The western wind carried the news quickly. The Ebonscale fleet lies useless, thanks to you. \\n\\nThe surprises from you never cease.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9902_0052_saboteur_v2",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 55,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9902_0052_d_00_container_saboteur_v2",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9902b_MSQ_Adiana",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_52",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_51",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9902_0052_saboteur_v2_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Saboteur",
        "Description": "Sabotage the Corrupted Fleet at the Dynasty Shipyard.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I'm off to sabotage the fleet.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Even if this works, your plan for the Motherwell is still insane. \\n\\nBut the Corrupted Ebonscale fleet is a very real threat, and I'll breathe easier knowing it's neutralized. \\n\\nGood luck.",
        "InProgressResponse": "The fleet is moored in Ebonscale, at the Dynasty Shipyards. \\n\\nExpect it to be very well-defended.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "The western wind carried the news quickly. The Ebonscale fleet lies useless, thanks to you. \\n\\nThe surprises from you never cease.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9902_0052_saboteur_solo",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 55,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9902_0052_d_00_container_saboteur_solo",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_52_b",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_52_b_Unlock",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9902_0052_saboteur_solo_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Hit the Decks",
        "Description": "As an alternative to attacking the Empress and her fleet in the Dynasty Shipyard Expediton, take the blight bombs and plant them in the cargo being brought out to the fleet. While you're there, defeat the Generals of the fleet to disrupt their leadership.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "",
        "InProgressResponse": "",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9907_0053_blessingofearth",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 56,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9907_0053_d_00_container_blessingofearth",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9902b_MSQ_Adiana",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_52a",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_52",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9907_0053_blessingofearth_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Blessings of Earth",
        "Description": "Make offerings to the villagers to gain their favor.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Who do I need to ask?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "You must make offerings to the denizens of this place.\\n\\nThey will be able to sense your intentions. If the offerings are accepted, you will have the blessing of the Angry Earth to carry out your plan.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Make your offerings to earn your blessing.\\n\\nI would suggest being very generous.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You continue to raise my expectations, {playerName}. \\n\\nIt would be difficult for me to destroy you if you were to betray the Angry Earth's trust.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9907_0053_blessingofearth_Juice",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 56,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9907_0053_d_00_container_blessingofearth_Task1",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9907_MSQ_AEVillager1",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_52b",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_52",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9907_0053_blessingofearth_Juice_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Juice's Blessing",
        "Description": "Bring a large fish to Juice the Bear.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What kind of offering?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "I do love fish, large ones.\\n\\nIt has been so long since I have had nice fish.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I'm still thinking about that fish.\\n\\nIt's quite distracting…",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Mmm. This is a very fine fish. It's been so long since I was brought an offering...",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9907_0053_blessingofearth_Snap",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 56,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9907_0053_d_00_container_blessingofearth_Task2",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9908_MSQ_AEVillager2",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_52c",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_52",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9907_0053_blessingofearth_Snap_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Snap's Blessing",
        "Description": "Find a momento of town life for Snap the Wolf.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Is there something I could do for you?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "I would like to understand humans more, before I grant any blessings.\\n\\nFind me a memento that demonstrates care.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I need something to ponder, something to chew over.\\n\\nFind me a token, perhaps a toy?",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "I wanted to know…how humans hold their pack. \\n\\nI wanted to learn… how creatures who forget, remember. \\n\\nI see now that they store their memories in things they make…very clever. \\n\\nThank you. Take my blessing.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9907_0053_blessingofearth_Ixia",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 56,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9907_0053_d_00_container_blessingofearth_Task3",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9906_MSQ_Shamaness",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_53",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_52",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9907_0053_blessingofearth_Ixia_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Ixia's Blessing",
        "Description": "Craft Ixia's plant food at an Arcane Repositary.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"How can I help?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "the tempest spreads corruption shades the sun \\n\\nmy people cannot make the food they need \\n\\nthrough crafting arts their suffering undone \\n\\nmy blessing cede",
        "InProgressResponse": "my people are hungry",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "The tempest spreads corruption shades the sun \\n\\nmy people cannot make the food they need \\n\\nthrough crafting arts their suffering undone \\n\\nmy blessing cede",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9902_0054_ASelflessNature",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": null,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9902_0054_d_00_container_ASelflessNature",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9902b_MSQ_Adiana",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_54",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_52a \u0026\u0026 99_MSQ_52b \u0026\u0026 99_MSQ_52c \u0026\u0026 99_MSQ_53",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9902_0054_ASelflessNature_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "A Selfless Nature",
        "Description": "Defeat the Guardian and Blight the Motherwell",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Trust me, Adiana.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "A word of warning. The sanctuary guardian will attack any non-Angry Earth creature who enters. \\n\\nAs the Motherwell is one of our great treasures, so the guardian is one of our great weapons.",
        "InProgressResponse": "The way into the sanctuary is open to you now. \\n\\nDefeat the guardian and do what you must to crush the Tempest.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "I can feel the Motherwell convulsing. The Blight flows through its world-spanning roots… \\n\\nAll the way to Shattered Mountain.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9902_0055_shatteredmountain",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9902_0055_d_00_container_shatteredmountain",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9910_MSQ_AEScout",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_55",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_54",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9902_0055_shatteredmountain_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Shattered Mountain",
        "Description": "Meet the Angry Earth scout in Shattered Mountain.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I'll use it responsibly.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "I know you will. It's time now for you to go the Shattered Mountain itself.\\n\\nSpeak with my friend Gristle at the forest's edge, and he will aid you on your way.",
        "InProgressResponse": "The time is now. Go to Shattered Mountain, and make Aeternum whole again.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Psst. You must be {playerName}. Adiana said you'd come. \\n\\nI'm Gristle, the scout. Is this your first time talking to a bear?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9910_0056_thetempestsheart",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9910_0056_d_00_container_thetempestsheart",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0717_Warden",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_56",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_55",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9910_0056_thetempestsheart_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Fortress at the Threshold",
        "Description": "Find the Soulwardens at Mountainhome Outpost, and offer your help.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"That's when the Tempest's soul touched shore.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Is that right? I bet the Corruption sensed it. \\n\\nHuman souls tend to be pretty noisy.",
        "InProgressResponse": "If you so happen back this way, feel free to bring some fish.\\n\\nSlim pickings around here.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Well, I was wondering if you'd ever join us here on the front lines. Though you might be too late. \\n\\nIf you haven't heard yet, we may be on the verge of abandoning this position.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9901_0057_insoulinstone",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9901_0057_d_00_container_insoulinstone",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0717_Warden",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_57",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_56",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9901_0057_insoulinstone_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "QuestReward_MSQFinale",
        "ItemRewardQty": 1,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "The Heart of the Tempest",
        "Description": "Enter the Tempest's Heart Expedition and look for the Tempest herself -  Captain Isabella - and then confront her and put an end to her campaign of Corruption.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I'm actually going in.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "I'm sorry… I think I misheard you. Did you say you need to check in at the inn? \\n\\nPerfectly understandable. I know you've been on a long journey. It's right over there, of course.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I'll say this much, you've got sand.\\n\\nGo on then - kick the Tempest's ass. The Soulwardens, those of us who remain,  we're behind you all the way.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Wow, you look like hell. It must've been a fight for the ages. We saw the change in the Mountain.\\n\\nDoes that mean… I can't believe I'm saying this - is the Tempest destroyed?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": true,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9910_0058_finallyexhale",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9910_0058_d_00_container_finallyexhale",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9905e_MSQ_Rima",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_58",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_57",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9910_0058_finallyexhale_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Finally, Exhale",
        "Description": "Tell your friends the good news.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I can't argue with that.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "I'm sure there are other people all over Aeternum who would welcome this news.\\n\\nI'll leave it to you to share the good word. Thank you, {playerName}. I never thought this day would come.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I think it's going to take some time for me to really internalize this turn of events.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "If we don't have hope, what do we have?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": true,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9905_0059_InMemoriam",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9910_0059_d_00_container_InMemoriam",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9928_MSQ_YonasMemorial",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_59",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99_MSQ_58",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9905_0059_InMemoriam_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "In Memoriam",
        "Description": "Gather tokens of remembrance from your companions, and set them at a memorial to Yonas at Fisherman's Bend.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "If we don't have hope, what do we have?",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "I've heard that some of the Soulwardens have built a memorial to Yonas at his old place by the river.\\n\\nHere's a token of my own favor, do you think you could go to Emile and Theo and ask them for their own?\\n\\nI think it would be best if you represented us all, and brought those tokens home to him.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I don't know if we will ever be able to put Old Yonas to rest, but we can memorialize his sacrifice, and his valor.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "(The cold stone sits, quietly inert)",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": true,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9926_0101_TenaciousRose",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 20,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9926_0101_d_00_container_TenaciousRose",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9926_VK_AbigailRoseB",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "VarangianKnights_0101",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9926_0101_TenaciousRose_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Tenacious Rose",
        "Description": "Mysterious Raiders have taken over the ruins of Stonereach Keep where Abigail Rose was living. She's asked you to help figure who they are, why they're here and how she can get rid of them.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Whoa, easy! You seem a bit jumpy.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Out here, that's a critical trait, lest you wind up Corrupted or Lost! \\n\\nAnd don't try to tell me a settlement would be safer! I'll not be trusting my fate to some bumbling constable!",
        "InProgressResponse": "Have you figured out what these trespassers are doing in my Keep?\\n\\nWhatever it takes to get rid of them, I'm up for it.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Ah, you dealt that laughing bastard a thrashing? Well done! The wolves finally met a more vicious wolf! \\n\\nThis doesn’t mean I trust you, by the way. But I can’t argue with your results. Did you learn why they're here?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9926_0103_LostScarecrow",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 28,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9926_0103_d_00_container_LostScarecrow",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9930_VK_RomacBarboB",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "VarangianKnights_0103",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9926_0103_LostScarecrow_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "The Lost Scarecrow",
        "Description": "Locate Abigail Rose's missing companion, and find any evidence that points to what the Varangian Knights are searching for.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What are you doing here?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "My partner and I have been watching this camp for some time, and he moved closer to get a better look. Keep hoping for some sign from him, but nothing yet.\\nView is limited, and the patrols are thick.\\n\\nYou... wouldn't be interested in helping me again, would you?",
        "InProgressResponse": "Stick to the shadows, move slowly... and when the time is right, take them down. That's how we'll get these fools off our land.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Thanks for your help back there. I'm going to rest here for a bit, then take the long way back to the south. Don't want to have any other accidental run-ins with those armored cretins. Much better at staying out of sight than in a brawl. Abigail will be waiting for my report.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": null
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9932_0104_RelicReclamation",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 30,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "9932_0104_d_00_container_RelicReclamation",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9931_VK_Caoimhe",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "VarangianKnights_0104",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9932_0104_RelicReclamation_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Relic Reclamation",
        "Description": "Find the notebook carried south by the Varangian Knights by speaking with the apprentice Caoimhe",
        "PlayerPrompt": "(Read the note)",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "To the one who finds this:\\nI have been taken by the Varangians, those cretins who seek to unlock the mysteries of Myrddin's experiments. Given my treatment at their hands, they won't use them for anything good.",
        "InProgressResponse": "You must head south. There is a woman there, Caoimhe, an apprentice to an Antiquarian. She is an ally, and familiar with the magics of the island.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Welcome back! Did you find the notebook for Romac?\\nWait, he wanted me to have it? If this holds the location to Myrddin's true workshop, this is a valuable - and dangerous - find. I... think I shall keep this from the Antiquarian. I know just where to hide it.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": null,
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": true
    }
]
